Evelyn Frech

Human Resources. Open to new opportunities/fluent in Spanish & English



evelynmariafrech@gmail.com

Orlando FL United States

OBJECTIVE

I'm 25 years old with a Business Management degree. Fluent in Spanish and English. I'm looking for a job that will challenge me everyday and where i can bring dynamism to the business and develop professional skills through performing and practicing the daily job.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Internship | The Competition Superintendence | El Salvador. C.A. | From 2008 to 2009

The Competition Superintendence is a government institution from the Republic of El Salvador and it mission is to investigate and punish anticompetitive practices. My role was to monitor the public procurement process to ensure the successful completion of these, according to competition law. This experience helped me have a clearer vision of running an organization, as well as having responsibilities and manage confidential information.

Volunteer - trainer | Dr. Jose Matías Delgado University | El Salvador, C.A. | From 2009 to 2009

I volunteered for this project which main objective was to encourage skilled poor women to develop a business idea and start their own business. I was responsible for providing motivational speaking, basic knowledge in business administration and workshops. The project began with a group of women near the capital. Then, the project grew and I had the opportunity to travel to Ataco town, located 3 hours-drive from the capital, to work with another group of women. I volunteered because I thought I could help a lot. This way I made my social hours at the Dr. Jose Matías Delgado University. The project was funded by the Austrian Development Cooperation.

Manager assistant | J.F. Lawn Services, LLC. | Orlando, Fl. | From 2011 to 2012

As a manager assistant some of the duties are: create, keep and manage customers' files, schedule weekly routes, Generate monthly billing (software quickbooks), Create and send proposals to customers, keep payment records, Keep works records, and help the manager with any task required.

EDUCATION

Dr. José Matías Delgado University | El Salvador, C.A | From 2006 to 2010

Area of Study/Major: Business Administration

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office suite Proficiency: Advanced
- Photoshop Proficiency: Basic Knowledge
- Time management Proficiency: Proficient
- Multitasking Proficiency: Proficient
- · Personal Coach Proficiency: Proficient

LANGUAGES

- Spanish Fluent
- English Fluent

HONORS & AWARDS

- Cum Laude graduated Dr. Jose Matías Delgado
- Dedication award Empowering Woman Project
- Innovating Idea award Dr. Jose Matías Delgado

JOB SEARCH DETAILS

Categories of Interest:Job Types:

Administrative, Executive Management, HR & Recruiting, Marketing, Nonprofit & Philanthropy Employee, Freelance, Seasonal, Volunteer, Full-Time, Part-Time, Occasional, Temporary, Internships, Alternative Schedule All Telecommuting Flexible Flexible 30-40

30-40

Flexible Schedule, Part-Time Schedule, Telecommuting, Freelancing Job Yes 13 USD / Hourly Entry-Level

Level of Telecommuting:
Start Date:
Availability:
Maximum Hours/Week:
Job Flexibility Preferences:
Willing to Travel:
Salary & Benefits:
Career level: